a cat with a white and black stripe on its face
Siberian Cat - Felis catus
a lone polar bear is standing in the middle of the water
Hawksbill Sea Turtle - Eretmochelys imbricata
an elephant walking through a grassy field
African Elephant - Loxodonta africana
a small brown and white animal eating a piece of food
Prairie Dog - Cynomys ludovicianus
a large brown bear eating a piece of food
Mandrill - Mandrillus sphinx
a small brown and white striped animal
Leopard - Panthera pardus
a brown and white cat with a green face
Eurasian Lynx - Lynx lynx
a zebra standing on top of a grass covered field
Nile Lechwe - Kobus megaceros
a cat standing on a rock near a pond
Eurasian Otter - Lutra lutra
a small bird sitting on a branch in a forest
Squirrel Monkey - Saimiri sciureus
a large brown bear standing on top of a rock
North American River Otter - Lontra canadensis
a small brown bear standing in the grass
Juvenile Cheetah - Acinonyx jubatus
a zebra walking through a grassy field
Cheetah (Masai Mara) - Acinonyx jubatus
a close up of a close up of a close up of a face
Cheetah (Close-Up) - Acinonyx jubatus
a zebra standing on top of a lush green field
Plains Zebra - Equus quagga
a brown and white striped animal standing in the grass
Lion - Panthera leo
a white dog standing in a grassy field
White Lion - Panthera leo
elephants are standing on the beach
Hippopotamus Pod - Hippopotamus amphibius
a large elephant walking through a dry area
African Elephant (Mud Bath) - Loxodonta africana
two zebras standing in a muddy area next to a body of water
Plains Zebra (Drinking) - Equus quagga
a large brown animal walking through a grassy area
Gray Wolf - Canis lupus
a herd of zebras grazing in a field
Plains Zebra & Blue Wildebeest - Equus quagga & Connochaetes taurinus
giraffes are walking through a field
Giraffe Family - Giraffa camelopardalis
a small white and black bird standing in a field
Pronghorn - Antilocapra americana
a small brown and white dog standing on a dirt field
Red Fox - Vulpes vulpes
a brown and white cow standing in a field
European Roe Deer - Capreolus capreolus
a black dog with a black collar and a black bow
Italian Mastiff (Puppy) - Canis lupus familiaris